[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120911pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", "TO", "VB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 28, "question": "Is there a connection here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 29, "answer": "Well, from what I have been led to believe, as I stand here, there's no connection yet identified as to the coordination.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120911pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "RB", "IN", "NNS", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 49, "question": "What do you make of this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 50, "answer": "They are in a really tough neighborhood and there's a lot of uncertainty now that surrounds them.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["United States"]}, "docId": "120911pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "WRB", ":", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "."], "qSentId": 70, "question": "What happened there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBN", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 71, "answer": "Well, I can tell you that clearly I walked out of the meeting with the understanding that the Israeli government is a little frustrated with the lack of certainty on where -- on behalf of the United States.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Netanyahu"]}, "docId": "120911pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ":", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 89, "question": "What's going on here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 90, "answer": "Well, I think that -- look, Prime Minister Netanyahu can reach the president any time he wants.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120911pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 101, "question": "As a strong supporter of Israel, what do you say?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 102, "answer": "Well, here's what I'd say.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Israel"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120911pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 130, "question": "On this 11th anniversary of 9/11, where do you see the greatest threat to the United States?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "CD", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "."], "aSentId": 131, "answer": "Well, here's another thing.", "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["11th anniversary of 9/11"], "LOCATION": ["United States"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["New York City Police Academy"], "PERSON": ["Pataki"]}, "docId": "120911pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "CD", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 176, "question": "Where were you exactly on that evening at 9:00 p.m. 11 years ago today?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "CD", "NNP", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 177, "answer": "I was at a temporary command center that Governor Pataki and I had set up at the New York City Police Academy on 22nd Street.", "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["11 years ago today"], "TIME": ["9:00 p.m."]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120911pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 206, "question": "When I look back on it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 207, "answer": "LITZER: Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120911pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 228, "question": "Is that possible?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 229, "answer": "Sure, sure.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120911pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 257, "question": "So what did you make of the Democrat's convention?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 258, "answer": "Well, I thought they were two very interesting conventions.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120911pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 290, "question": "...that would allow that to once again come into play?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "DT", "MD", "VB", "IN", "TO", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 291, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["'07", "'08"]}, "docId": "120911pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "RB", "CD", "NNS", ",", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBG", "IN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 304, "question": "And Mitt Romney participated when you did it as well?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 305, "answer": "Well I mean I debated Mitt maybe 11 times, 12 times in '07, going into '08.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Paul Ryan", "Joe Biden"]}, "docId": "120911pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "MD", "VB", "RB", "RB", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RP", "VBG", "DT", "JJR", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 331, "question": "That could be lively?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "MD", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 332, "answer": "That will be very lively and it ends up being a more important debate for Paul Ryan than it does for Joe Biden.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["September 11th"]}, "docId": "120911pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "CD", ":", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 376, "question": "Howard, let me ask you, how are you doing tonight?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 377, "answer": "Every year on September 11th -- and you know it's the toughest day in the world for us.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120911pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "POS", "NN", "NN", "CC", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 395, "question": "How did you learn that a plane -- yes, a plane had crashed into the North Tower?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "DT", "NN", ":", "NNS", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 396, "answer": "I was standing in front of my son's nursery school or Kindergarten.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120911pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "RP", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 423, "question": "What did he tell her?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 424, "answer": "You know, my sister picked up the phone and my sister, Edi, runs our relief fund.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Broker Tech"]}, "docId": "120911pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "CD", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", ",", "IN", "DT", "VBD", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 466, "question": "Why was it so important to reopen so quickly?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 467, "answer": "Well, one of our competitors named Broker Tech was really pushing to open, because this was their big chance, you know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120911pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 492, "question": "You think they should change that or try to change that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "CC", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 493, "answer": "I'll tell anybody -- I'm telling you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120911pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 498, "question": "But do you worry about future terror threats in New York?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 499, "answer": "Of course.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New York"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120911pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RBR", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 505, "question": "Are you thinking -- are you thinking all of us are better prepared now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RBR", "VBN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 506, "answer": "Well, I'm certain that we are better prepared.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120911pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", ":", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 545, "question": "You want to tell our viewers which candidate you are leaning toward?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "WDT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 546, "answer": "You know, I'm probably leaning -- in the presidential race toward Romney.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]